{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
<<<<<<< HEAD
      "question": "What are the eigenvalues of the matrix [[3, 0],[0, 4]]",
=======
      "question": "1. What are the eigenvalues of the matrix [[3, 0],[0, 4]]",
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
      "answers": {
        "a": "1,2",
        "b": "3,4",
        "c": "2,3",
        "d": "4,5"
      },
      "explanations": {
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "a": "Explanation 2",
        "b": "For a diagonal matrix, the eigenvalues are the diagonal elements.",
        "c": "Explanation 2",
        "d": "Explanation 2"
=======
        "a": "Not correct",
        "b": "For a diagonal matrix, the eigenvalues are the diagonal elements.",
        "c": "Not correct",
        "d": "Not correct"
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
<<<<<<< HEAD
      "question": "Which vector is an eigenvector of the matrix [[2, 0],[0, 3]]",
=======
      "question": "2. Which vector is an eigenvector of the matrix [[2, 0],[0, 3]]",
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
      "answers": {
        "a": "[1 0]",
        "b": "[0 1]",
        "c": "[1 1]",
        "d": "Both a and b"
      },
      "explanations": {
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "a": "Explanation 2",
        "b": "Explanation 2",
        "c": "Explanation 2",
=======
        "a": "Not correct",
        "b": "Not correct",
        "c": "Not correct",
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
        "d": "[1 0] is an eigenvector for eigenvalue 2, and [0 1] is an eigenvector for eigenvalue 3."
      },
      "correctAnswer": "d",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
<<<<<<< HEAD
      "question": "Eigenvalue decomposition of a matrix involves decomposing the matrix into which form?",
=======
      "question": "3. Eigenvalue decomposition of a matrix involves decomposing the matrix into which form?",
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
      "answers": {
        "a": "A = PDP^-1",
        "b": "A = LDU",
        "c": "A = LUP",
        "d": "A = LQU"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "A = PDP^-1, where P is the matrix of eigenvectors and D is the diagonal matrix of eigenvalues.",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "b": "Explanation 2",
        "c": "Explanation 2",
        "d": "Explanation 2"
=======
        "b": "Not correct",
        "c": "Not correct",
        "d": "Not correct"
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
<<<<<<< HEAD
      "question": "LU Decomposition of a matrix A is represented as:",
=======
      "question": "4. LU Decomposition of a matrix A is represented as:",
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
      "answers": {
        "a": "A=LU",
        "b": "A=UL",
        "c": "A=PLU",
        "d": "A=PQU"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "LU decomposition expresses A as a product of a lower triangular matrix L and an upper triangular matrix U",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "b": "Explanation 2",
        "c": "Explanation 2",
        "d": "Explanation 2"
=======
        "b": "Not correct",
        "c": "Not correct",
        "d": "Not correct"
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
<<<<<<< HEAD
      "question": "SVD of a matrix A is represented as",
=======
      "question": "5. SVD of a matrix A is represented as",
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
      "answers": {
        "a": "A = UΣV",
        "b": "A = UVΣ^T",
        "c": "A = UΣV^T",
        "d": "A = UΣV*"
      },
      "explanations": {
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "a": "Explanation 2",
        "b": "Explanation 2",
        "c": "In SVD, A is decomposed into U ,Σ(a digonal matrix) and V^T.",
        "d": "Explanation 2"
=======
        "a": "Not correct",
        "b": "Not correct",
        "c": "In SVD, A is decomposed into U ,Σ(a diagonal matrix) and V^T.",
        "d": "Not correct"
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
<<<<<<< HEAD
      "question": "The result of multiplying [[1, 2], [3, 4]] and [[2, 0], [1, 2]]",
=======
      "question": "6. The result of multiplying [[1, 2], [3, 4]] and [[2, 0], [1, 2]]",
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
      "answers": {
        "a": "[[4, 4], [10, 8]]",
        "b": "[[2, 4], [7, 10]]",
        "c": "[[4, 4], [7, 10]]",
        "d": "[[4, 4], [10, 10]]"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "Multiplying the matrices results in [[1.2 + 2.1, 1.0 + 2.2], [3.2 + 4.1, 3.0 + 4.2]]=[[4, 4], [10, 8]]",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "b": "Explanation 2",
        "c": "Explanation 2",
        "d": "Explanation 2"
=======
        "b": "Not correct",
        "c": "Not correct",
        "d": "Not correct"
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
<<<<<<< HEAD
      "question": "The result of adding [[1, 2], [3, 4]] and [[2, 0], [1, 2]]",
=======
      "question": "7. The result of adding [[1, 2], [3, 4]] and [[2, 0], [1, 2]]",
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
      "answers": {
        "a": "[[2, 0], [1, 2]]",
        "b": "[[3, 2], [3, 6]]",
        "c": "[[1, 2], [3, 4]]",
        "d": "[[3, 2], [4, 6]]"
      },
      "explanations": {
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "a": "Explanation 2",
        "b": "Explanation 2",
        "c": "Explanation 2",
=======
        "a": "Not correct",
        "b": "Not correct",
        "c": "Not correct",
>>>>>>> bfb9e6c (Dev Files)
        "d": "Adding the matrices results in [[1+2, 2+0], [3+1, 4+2]]=[[3, 2], [4, 6]]"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "d",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    }
  ]
}
